Inspired by a true story
From Straight A's to XXX is a drama, tv movie film directed by Vanessa Parise.
When a change of circumstances leaves Miriam unable to pay her college tuition, she makes a
surprising decision: to start performing in adult films, using the pseudonym Belle Knox.
Miriam lies to her family and her friends at school,
keeping her double life a secret.
But soon rumours spread and Miriam becomes the subject of
vicious online attacks and unwanted attention.
Miriam fights back: she talks to the media, saying her new
line of work empowers her as a feminist.
But her confident stand has unintended consequences.
Miriam is shunned by her conservative family and her
colleagues in the adult film world.
One impulsive decision has quickly spiralled out of control
- and Miriam's problems are just beginning.
Miriam Weeks, played by Haley Pullos.
Jolie, played by Sasha Clements.
Don, played by Judd Nelson.
Dora, played by Alyson Bath.
Amy, played by Jacky Lai.
Amanda, played by Jessica Lu.
XXX may refer to:
The tone is emotional.